<resources>
    <string name="app_name">iBusChina监护人</string>
    
    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">Incorrect password</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">Required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_student">添加学生</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_web_view">WebViewActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pwd">修改密码</string>

    <string name="not_updated_yet">Not updated yet</string>
    <string name="updated_at">Updated at %1$s before</string>
    <string name="updated_just_now">Updated Just Now</string>
    <string name="time_error">Time error!</string>

    <string name="head">这里是HeadView</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh">下拉刷新</string>
    <string name="release_to_refresh">释放立即刷新</string>
    <string name="refreshing">正在刷新...</string>
    <string name="refresh_succeed">刷新成功</string>
    <string name="refresh_fail">刷新失败</string>
    <string name="pullup_to_load">上拉加载更多</string>
    <string name="release_to_load">释放立即加载</string>
    <string name="loading">正在加载...</string>
    <string name="load_succeed">加载成功</string>
    <string name="load_fail">加载失败</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">Sign Up</string>
    <string name="airplus_content1">AirPlus is to monitor your indoor air quality after implementation of the air filtration project.

Using the top level of indoor air quality monitor,the measurement data will be collected by our server on the cloud and accessed seamlessly form your mobile device.

</string>
        <string name="airplus_content2">AirPlus is ideal for educational,commerical,hospitality,healthcare,fitness or residential environment where air quality really matters.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_list">ContactListActivity</string>
    <string name="bsn_content">
        Introduction
简介
World Class Education
世界级一流教育

The British School of Nanjing offers a modern and vibrant education to boys and girls in Early Years, Primary and Secondary School. The school serves expatriate families looking to provide their children with a private education of the highest standard. We nurture high aspirations for each and every one of our students. Many achieve great academic results while others discover a passion or special talent. Our day-to-day focus is on helping pupils to thrive in their own unique way.

南京英国学校旨在为全世界的幼儿、小学及中学生提供现代化并充满活力的教育。学校服务于希望子女得到一流私立教育的外籍家庭并致力于培养每一名学生志存高远。我们培养很多学生取得了优异的成绩，而更多的人发现了自身的天赋和才能。这都要归功于我们日常关注的重点——帮助每一名学生以自己独特的方式茁壮成长。

We offer a rich and varied curriculum based on the English National Curriculum that allows pupils to explore the breadth and depth of their abilities. Work is underpinned by a highly qualified and dedicated teaching body. Small class sizes and low student to teacher ratios mean that pupils can receive the support they require to make good progress both academically and in their personal development.

我们提供以英式教育为基础，丰富多样的课程，让学生去探索自身能力的广度和深度。高素质的专业教师队伍、小班制和学生与教师的恰当比例都保证了学生可以最大程度上获得学业及个人全方面发展的支持。

The school enjoys a vibrant day-to-day life with children participating in Music, Drama, Arts, and Sports programs as well as a number of other Enrichment activities.

孩子们可以在学校通过参加音乐，艺术，戏剧表演，体育运动及其他各种丰富的活动来度过充实而有趣的一天。

BSN has preserved a strong sense of community since its foundation and every member of the school has many opportunities to contribute to the welfare of the school community. We are proud of the role our families play in our school and in turn the role we play in their lives during their time in Nanjing.

自成立以来，南京英国学校一直保持着强烈的集体主义精神，每一位在校师生都有很多机会为学校这个大家庭作出自己的贡献；我们为那些成为学校一员的家庭感到自豪，也为我们能在众多家庭的南京生活时光中添上一笔而感到荣幸。

BSN is part of the British Schools Foundation, a network of 11 leading schools in America, Europe and Asia.

南京英国学校是英国学校集团旗下的一所学校，我们在北美、欧洲和亚洲共有11所学校。

For more information or to arrange a tour of the school please call us on +86 25 5210 8987 or email info@bsn.org.cn.

如需了解更多信息或需预约参观学校，请致电+86 2552108987或发邮件至info@bsn.org.cn。

    </string>
</resources>
